A Guide to the Photographs of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1993
Library of Virginia
- 90-8775, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Head Start Day, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- 90-8776, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Arthritis Awareness Week, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- 90-8777, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Month of the Child, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- 90-8778, Gov. Wilder attends a press conference for VASAPA, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- 90-8779, Gov. Wilder attends a press conference for VASAPA, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- 90-8780, Gov. Wilder signs HB 511, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- 90-8781, Gov. Wilder signs HB 91, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- 90-8782, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1117, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- 90-8786, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for National Credit Education Week, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 90-8798, Old Senate Chamber Courtesy Call, 5/25/1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- 90-8799, South African lawyer visits Gov. Wilder, 5/25/1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- 90-8806, Gov. Wilder has a press conference and names people to committee, 5/30/1990 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- 90-8829, Gov. Wilder has a press conference and names people to committee, 5/30/1990 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- 90-8846, Miss Teenage Virginia visits with Gov. Wilder, 5/31/1990 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- 90-8847, Miss Teenage Virginia visits with Gov. Wilder, 5/31/1990 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- 90-8854, Angola Delegation visits with Gov. Wilder, 5/31/1990 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- 90-8877, Portrait of Lt. Gov. Donald Beyers, 6/4/1990 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- 90-8878, Portrait of Lt. Gov. Donald Beyers, 6/4/1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- 90-8882, Gov. Wilder has the Governor's Fellows Picnic at the Mansion, 6/4/1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- 90-8883, Gov. Wilder has the Governor's Fellows Picnic at the Mansion, 6/4/1990 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- 90-8884, Gov. Wilder has the Governor's Fellows Picnic at the Mansion, 6/4/1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- 90-8889, Gov. Wilder visits with AAA Poster Winners, 6/5/1990 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- 90-8898, The Ambassador from Japan visits with Gov. Wilder, 6/7/1990 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- 90-8905, Finnish Executive presents the Gov. Wilder a gift, 6/7/1990 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- 90-8943, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Safety Week, 6/12/1990 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- 90-8944, Gov. Wilder signs Independence for Richmond from violence, 6/12/1990 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- 90-8946, Gov. Wilder presents achievement awards from the State Library, 6/12/1990 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- 90-8947, Gov. Wilder presents awards for Drug Free Schools, 6/12/1990 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- 90-9001, Prince Bandar bin Sultan bin Abdulaziz from Saudi Arabia visits with Gov. Wilder, 6/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- 90-9002, Winners of the American Co-Ed Pageant visit with Gov. Wilder, 6/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- 90-9060, People from the PKU party came to visit Gov. Wilder, 6/29/1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- 90-9063, Virginia Federation of Women Clubs presented a gift to Gov. Wilder, 7/2/1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 90-9064, Andy Fox makes a visit to Gov. Wilder, 7/2/1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- 90-9065, Gov. Wilder is presented United States Flag, 7/2/1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- No id number, Naturalization Ceremony Monticello, 7/4/1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- 90-9080, The Home Builders Association of Virginia meets with Gov. Wilder, 7/9/1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- 90-9081, Allegheny Regional Commission meets with Gov. Wilder, 7/9/1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- 90-9089, Gov. Wilder presents a CFR to Peter Decker, 7/11/1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- 90-9143, Gov. Wilder addresses commissions on Health Care, 7/18/1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- 90-9144, Gov. Wilder addresses commission on Health Care, 7/18/1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- 90-9170, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Weatherization, 7/9/1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- 90-9171, Mr. and Mrs. Zapp visit with Gov. Wilder, 7/19/1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- 90-9172, Secretary John Milliken and citizen talk with Gov. Wilder about Route 234, 7/19/1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- 90-9186, Calvin Edwards visits with Gov. Wilder, 7/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- 90-9187, Calvin Edwards visits with Gov. Wilder, 7/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- 90-9188, Calvin Edwards visits with Gov. Wilder, 7/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- 90-9189, Gov. Wilder holds an open house for the citizens, 7/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- 90-9190, Gov. Wilder holds an open house for the citizens, 7/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- 90-9191, Gov. Wilder holds an open house for the citizens, 7/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- 90-9242, Brady Pittman scholarship winners visit with Gov. Wilder, 7/24/1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- 90-9285, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Stephanie Lane Hoofnagle, 7/27/1990 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- 90-9286, Gov. Wilder is photographed with the Governors Fellows, 7/27/1990 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- 90-9313, Gov. Wilder meets with member of the Legislature on budget, 8/2/1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- 90-9314, Gov. Wilder meets with agency heads about the budget, 8/2/1990 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- 90-9354, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Professional Week, 8/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- 90-9355, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Cooperative Education, 8/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- 90-9356, Gov. Wilder with winners of American Co-Ed pageant, 8/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- 90-9360, Gov. Wilder meets with students who are traveling to Angola, 8/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- 90-9361, Gov. Wilder meets with students who are traveling to Angola, 8/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- 90-9385, Gov. Wilder holds 2nd Open House for citizens, 8/11/1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- 90-9386, Gov. Wilder holds 2nd Open House for citizens, 8/11/1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- 90-9391, Att. Gen. Mary Sue Terry signs settlement agreement, 8/13/1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- 90-9406, Gov. Wilder visits with people from his Alma Mater Norfolk State, 8/15/1990 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- 90-9407, Gov. Wilder speaks with Boy Scouts and Cub Scouts from Hampton, 8/15/1990 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- 90-9408, Gov. Wilder speaks with Boy Scouts and Cub Scouts from Hampton, 8/15/1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- 90-9438, Virginia 4H Peanut Sales kick-off presented peanuts to Gov. Wilder, 8/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- 90-9439, Home Builders Association Education Foundation Scholarship winner visit with Gov. Wilder, 8/21/1990 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- 90-9446, 1990 Charitable Campaign members with Gov. Wilder, 8/23/1990 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- 90-9452, Presentation of Academy of Excellence for Finance Reporting Award to Gov. Wilder, 8/24/1990 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- 90-9455, Decoration for Gov. Wilder's Dinner Party at the Mansion, 8/24/1990 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- 90-9456, Decoration for Gov. Wilder's Dinner Party at the Mansion, 8/24/1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- 90-9465, Gov. Wilder talks with a group from JTPA, 8/28/1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- 90-9466, Dr. Thornton and group visits with Gov. Wilder, 8/28/1990 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- 90-9486, Gov. Wilder held a press conference for the Bicentennial of the Bill of Rights, 9/4/1990 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- 90-9487, Lt. Gov. Don Beyer receives a check from Virginia Power, 9/5/1990 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- 90-9508, Members of the Patriots Foundation visit with Gov. Wilder, 9/6/1990 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- 90-9509, Ambassador Edward J. Perkins visits with Gov. Wilder, 9/6/1990 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- 90-9520, Gov. Wilder presents a CFR to the Native American Indians of Virginia, 9/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- 90-9521, Gov. Wilder presents a CFR to the Native American Indians of Virginia, 9/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- 90-9522, Charitable Campaign kick-off, Wilder attended, 9/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- 90-9523, Correction presents a certificate to Gov. Wilder, 9/7/1990 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- 90-9539, Gov. Wilder receives an award, 9/12/1990 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- 90-9540, Gov. Wilder meets with a occupational therapy group, 9/12/1990 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- 90-9550, Gov. Wilder visited by Arnie Armadillo, 9/13/1990 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- 90-9568, Gov. Wilder attends a Road Dedication for Route 23, 9/14/1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- 90-9569, Gov. Wilder rides in a Parade in Abingdon, 9/15/1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- 90-9570, Gov. Wilder rides in a Parade in Abingdon, 9/15/1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- 90-9571, Gov. Wilder makes an announcement on Dual Party Relay Center in Norton, 9/14/1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- 90-9572, Gov. Wilder holds an Open House in Abingdon, Virginia, 9/15/1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- 90-9574, Gov. Wilder holds an Open House in Abingdon, Virginia, 9/15/1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- 90-9575, Gov. Wilder attends a reception after the Dual Party Relay Center Announcement, 9/14/1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- 90-9576, Gov. Wilder attends a reception in the town of Lebanon, 9/14/1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- 90-9584, Gov. Wilder is presented a book by people from MCV, 9/18/1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- 90-9585, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR fir Virginians Against Domestic Violence, 9/18/1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- 90-9586, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for World Food Day, 9/18/1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- 90-9587, Yokohana Rubber Corporation Executives meet with Gov. Wilder, 9/18/1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- 90-9606, Gov. Wilder does PSA for DMV at the Mansion, 9/20/1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- 90-9607, Gov. Wilder holds a pledge Bond Breakfast at the Mansion, 9/20/1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- 90-9608, Gov. Wilder holds a press conference for the Pledge Bond Refence, 9/20/1990 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- 90-9637, Gov. Wilder attends Gov.'s Day at the State Fair of Virginia, 9/25/1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- 90-9638, Gov. Wilder attends Gov.'s Day at the State Fair of Virginia, 9/25/1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- 90-9639, Gov. Wilder attends Gov.'s Day at the State Fair of Virginia, 9/25/1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- 90-9640, Gov. Wilder attends Gov.'s Day at the State Fair of Virginia, 9/25/1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- 90-9641, Gov. Wilder attends Gov.'s Day at the State Fair of Virginia, 9/25/1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- 90-9647, Gov. Wilder talks with representatives of C & P and AT & T Corporation, 9/26/1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- 90-9663, Gov. Wilder talks with a Russian Delegation at the Capitol, 9/28/1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- 90-9665, Gov. Wilder relaxes with a book in his rocking chair, 9/28/1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- 90-9711, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Physical Therapy Month, 10/5/1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- 90-9712, Infant Mortality group meets with Gov. Wilder, 10/4/1990 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- 90-9713, Gov. Wilder being interviewed by Ebony magazine, 10/2/1990 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- 90-9714, Chefs Association presented a Chocolate State Seal to Gov. Wilder, 10/4/1990 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- 90-9715, Gov. Wilder addresses the Community Crime Prevention Luncheon, 10/2/1990 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- 90-9716, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for VAASA, 10/5/1990 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- 90-9717, Gov. Wilder presents Community Crime Prevention Awards, 10/2/1990 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- 90-9718, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Share-A-Songs, 10/3/1990 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- 90-9719, Gov. Wilder with Senator Scott and Friends, 10/5/1990 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- 90-9720, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Virginia Apple Month, 10/5/1990 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- 90-9721, Gov. Wilder visits with USIA African Delegation, 10/3/1990 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- 90-9722, Gov. Wilder signs the CFR for Lupus Awareness Month, 10/5/1990 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- 90-9723, Planned Parenthood meets with Gov. Wilder, 10/4/1990 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- 90-9724, Gov. Wilder addresses Southern Legislative Summit on Infant Morality, 10/4/1990 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- 90-9725, Staff members held a surprise party for Lou Bell, 10/3/1990 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- 90-9751, Gov. Wilder signs boards for Salvation Army Boys and Girls Club, 10/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- 90-9752, Gov. Wilder talks with Mrs. Unah, 10/3/1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 90-9753, Gov. Wilder dedicates latest section of Route 288 in Chesterfield County, 10/12/1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 90-9754, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Discovery Week, 10/12/1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- 90-9755, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Discovery Week, 10/12/1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- 90-9756, Miss Virginia Kelly Murray visits Gov. Wilder, 10/12/1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- 90-9757, Gov. Wilder visits with Mr. K. Imamura and group, 10/12/1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- 90-9758, Delma Francis mother visits with Gov. Wilder, 10/12/1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- 90-9759, Secretary Kemp addresses the Gov. conference on Housing, 10/15/1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- 90-9761, Delegate Shirley Cooper Yorktown Trustees and elected officials from France visits with Gov. Wilder, 10/16/1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 90-9763, Gov. Wilder holds the 3rd Open House in Norfolk, Virginia, 10/20/1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- 90-9764, Gov. Wilder holds the 3rd Open House in Norfolk, Virginia, 10/20/1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 90-9827, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Spinal Health Month, 10/22/1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- 90-9828, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Jewish Women Week, 10/22/1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- 90-9829, Gov. Wilder addresses the Senior Convocation Ceremony at Henrico High School, 11/1/1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- 90-9830, Gov. Wilder addresses the Senior Convocation Ceremony at Henrico High School, 11/1/1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- 90-9834, Gov. Wilder holds 5th open house for citizens of NoVa at George Mason University, 11/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- 90-9835, Gov. Wilder holds 5th Open House for the citizen of Northern Virginia at George Mason University, 11/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- 90-9836, Gov. Wilder holds 5th Open House for the citizen of Northern Virginia at George Mason University, 11/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- 90-9837, Gov. Wilder holds 5th Open House for the citizen of Northern Virginia at George Mason University, 11/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- 90-9839, Gov. Wilder has lunch with contest winners from grades 1-12, 11/15/1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- 90-9840, Gov. Wilder has lunch with contest winners from grades 1-12, 11/15/1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- 90-9841, Mr. Rucker, Mrs Shewl and Dr. Vaughan present a copy of the Bill of Rights to Gov. Wilder, 11/15/1990 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- 90-9842, Gov. Wilder with revenue forecast and General Assembly member, 11/20/1990 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- 90-9843, Gov. Wilder accepts tax payment from the Mattaponi and Pamunkey Indians tribes, 11/20/1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- 90-9844, Gov. Wilder accepts tax payment from the Mattaponi and Pamunkey Indians tribes, 11/20/1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- 90-9845, Gov. Wilder accepts tax payment from the Mattaponi and Pamunkey Indians tribes, 11/20/1990 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- 90-9846, Annual Toys for Tots Campaign was kicked off by Gov. Wilder and the Marine Corps, 11/26/1990 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- 90-9847, Gov. Wilder meets with Richmond Philharmonic & the composer who is creating a composition in his honor, 11/27/1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- 90-9848, Gov. Wilder with a group of children during a shooting of a PSA, 12/4/1990 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- 90-9849, Virginia Tree Grower Association presented a Christmas Tree the Gov. Wilder, 12/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- 90-9850, Virginia Tree Grower Association presented a Christmas Tree the Gov. Wilder, 12/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- 90-9851, 1st Annual Human Rights Conference was addresses by Gov. Wilder, 12/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- 90-9852, 1st Annual Human Rights Conference was addresses by Gov. Wilder, 12/10/1990 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- 90-9854, Christmas Decorations inside of the Gov.'s Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- 90-9855, Christmas Decorations inside of the Gov.'s Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- 90-9856, Christmas Decorations inside of the Gov.'s Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- 90-9857, Christmas Decorations inside of the Gov.'s Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- 90-9865, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Virginia Pharmacies Week, 10/22/1990 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- 91-0094, Gov. Wilder gives State of the State address to the Joint General Assembly, 1/9/1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- 91-0095, Gov. Wilder gives State of the State address to the Joint General Assembly, 1/9/1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- 91-0096, Gov. Wilder gives State of the State address to the Joint General Assembly, 1/9/1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- 91-0097, Gov. Wilder addresses National Gov.'s Meeting on Agriculture and Rural Development, 1/9/1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- 91-0099, Gov. Wilder press conference for joint signing of agency working together, 1/15/1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 91-0100, Presentation of Virginia Bill of Rights to Attorney General Mary Sue Terry, 1/15/1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 91-0101, Gov. Wilder addresses The New European Market Group Meeting, 1/15/1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- 91-0102, Gov. Wilder addresses The New European Market Group Meeting, 1/15/1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- 91-0103, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Virginia State University, 1/16/1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- 91-0105, Gov. Wilder attends a play at George Mason Elementary, 1/18/1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- 91-0106, Gov. Wilder attends a play at George Mason Elementary, 1/18/1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- 91-0107, Gov. Wilder attends a play at George Mason Elementary, 1/18/1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- 91-0108, Gov. Wilder attends a play at George Mason Elementary, 1/18/1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- 91-0109, Gov. Wilder attends a play at George Mason Elementary, 1/18/1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- 91-0110, Miss Virginia State Fair visits with family and Gov. Wilder, 1/18/1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- 91-0111, Gov. Wilder addresses Child Advocacy Day meeting, 1/22/1991 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- 91-0112, Gov. Wilder addresses Child Advocacy Day meeting, 1/22/1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- 91-0113, Certification of City's presented to Galax and Radford by Gov. Wilder, 1/22/1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- 91-0114, Gov. Wilder presents Grocer of the Year Award, 1/22/1991 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- 91-0115, Gov. Wilder addresses Youth at Drug and Alcohol Seminar, 1/22/1991 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- 91-0116, Exterior photographs of the Executive Mansion, 1/22/1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- 91-0118, Gov. Wilder awards the Chamber of Commerce Valor Awards to this year's winners, 1/24/1991 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- 91-0119, Gov. Wilder awards the Chamber of Commerce Valor Awards to this year's winners, 1/24/1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- 91-0120, Gov. Wilder meets with the members of the Fraternal Order of Police, 1/24/1991 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- 91-0121, Gov. Wilder meets with Congressional Delegation at the Gov.'s Mansion, 1/25/1991 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- 91-0122, Gov. Wilder meets with Congressional Delegation at the Gov.'s Mansion, 1/25/1991 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- 91-0123, Gov. Wilder is presented a Dental Travel Kit, 1/25/1991 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- 91-0124, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for School Board Member Appreciation Week, 1/25/1991 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- 91-0125, Gov. Wilder awards McDonald Black History week Awards, 1/25/1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- 91-0126, Gov. Wilder awards McDonald Black History week Awards, 1/25/1991 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- 91-0127, Gov. Wilder addresses Rally of Virginia Nurses Association, 1/28/1991 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- 91-0128, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Cardiac Rehabilitation Weeks, 1/29/1991 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- 91-0129, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for American Heart Month, 1/29/1991 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- 91-0130, Gov. Wilder meets with Sickle Cell Poster Child, 1/29/1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- 91-0131, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Engineer's Week, 1/29/1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- 91-0132, VEGA group meets with Gov. Wilder, 1/30/1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- 91-0133, Gov. Wilder addresses Professional Women's Club, 1/30/1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- 91-0134, Students for George Washington High School visits with Gov. Wilder, 1/30/1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- 91-0135, Gov. Wilder visits with Loudoun County High School Key Club, 1/31/1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- 91-0136, Film crew shooting Gov. Wilder for a movie about George Mason, 1/31/1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- 91-0137, The Statler Brothers visit with Gov. Wilder and the General Assembly and received an award, 2/1/1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- 91-0138, The Statler Brothers visit with Gov. Wilder and the General Assembly and received an award, 2/1/1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- 91-0139, The Statler Brothers visit with Gov. Wilder and the General Assembly and received an award, 2/1/1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- 91-0140, The Statler Brothers visit with Gov. Wilder and the General Assembly and received an award, 2/1/1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- 91-0141, Youth Gov. meets with Gov. Wilder, 2/1/1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- 91-0142, Gov. Wilder visits with students from South Anna Elementary school, 2/1/1991 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- 91-0143, Gov. Wilder visits with Girls scouts who delivered cookies, 2/1/1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- 91-0144, Former Ambassador to Kuwait, W. Nathaniel Howell III visits with Gov. Wilder, 2/6/1991 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- 91-0145, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for National Girls and Women in Sports Day, 2/7/1991 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- 91-0146, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Vocational Education Week, 2/7/1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- 91-0147, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Mental Retardation Month, 2/7/1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- 91-0148, Gov. Wilder presents Gov.'s Sports League Trophies, 2/7/1991 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- 91-0149, National President Ladies Auxiliary to Veterans of Foreign Wars visits with Gov. Wilder, 2/7/1991 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- 91-0150, Gov. Wilder addresses a group from AFS International Programs, 2/7/1991 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- 91-0151, Gov. Wilder with Emily Sydnor and Nikki Perrin pages for the House of Delegates, 2/8/1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- 91-0152, Gov. Wilder visits with Mr. And Mrs C.E. Field when they pay a courtesy call, 2/8/1991 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- 91-0153, Gov. Wilder visits with Stephen and Brandon Hill on Minority Op's in Virginia, 2/8/1991 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- 91-0154, Gov. Wilder is presented Youth Drug Pledge card from the Kiwanis Club of Clarke County, 2/7/1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- 91-0155, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Life Insurance Week, 2/13/1991 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- 91-0156, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for the Council for Exceptional Children, 2/13/1991 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- 91-0157, Gov. Wilder holds a Annual Pages Breakfast at the Executive Mansion, 2/14/1991 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- 91-0158, Nathaniel Church and his parents Sam and Patty Church visit with Gov. Wilder, 2/14/1991 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- 91-0159, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for 50th Anniversary of the Coast Guard, 2/19/1991 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- 91-0160, Gov. Wilder holds a press meeting with Ambassador Jacques Andre'an and Jean Yues Defay Council General from France, 2/19/1991 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- 91-0161, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Early Intervention Month, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- 91-0162, Gov. Wilder meets students from St. Williams Byrd High School, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- 91-0163, Gov. Wilder meets with the Cultural Enrichment Zeta Chi Omega group of young ladies, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- 91-0164, Gov. Wilder visits Foreign Exchange Officers and High School students, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- 91-0165, Gov. Wilder meets with Officials from Canon Corporation Executives, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- 91-0166, Gov. Wilder holds CIAA reception at the Governor's Executive Mansion, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- 91-0167, Gov. Wilder holds CIAA reception at the Governor's Executive Mansion, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- 91-0168, Gov. Wilder holds CIAA reception at the Governor's Executive Mansion, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- 91-0169, Gov. Wilder holds CIAA reception at the Governor's Executive Mansion, 2/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- 91-0170, Gov. Wilder meets with the Governor's Interns, 2/22/1991 (Box 11, Folder 41)